<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nishant Gadihoke</title>
    <link>https://nishantgadihoke.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Nishant Gadihoke</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 13:41:15 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://nishantgadihoke.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Oswald Labs</title>
      <link>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/oswald-labs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 13:41:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/oswald-labs/</guid>
      <description>About the project I co-founded Oswald Labs with Anand Chowdhary and Mahendra Singh Raghuwanshi in 2016 with the aim of creating technology which was accessible to everyone. Over the past few years, running this startup has taken up the majority of my time. Being a research-driven company, caring about user experience and building empathy is key to shaping our products.
While it is not possible to explain the nuances of this mega-project within the scope of this webpage, you can scroll down to read a brief description of each of the products we are currently working on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indikala</title>
      <link>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/indikala/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 13:55:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/indikala/</guid>
      <description>About the project Indikala is Asia&amp;rsquo;s premier online store for Indian handicrafts and home decor.
I led the design team to overhaul the visual identity of the store as it debuted in European and North American markets. The task was to create a unique and memorable visual identity which would resonate with existing customers and would help increase conversion rates for new ones.
The process Before rushing in to create a new brand identity, it was important to examine the previous one and observe where it worked and where it didn’t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Naari</title>
      <link>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/naari/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 13:42:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/naari/</guid>
      <description>About the project Naari is the end-to-end period healthcare companion—from giving you personalized tampon recommendations using P&amp;amp;G’s survey data and HPE’s machine learning APIs, to getting those products delivered to your doorstep via Amazon.
 Great use of machine learning to drive a benefit for women.
– Erik Hasenoehrl, Research Fellow, Procter &amp;amp; Gamble
 Naari is also a social platform that lets you chat with your doctor, friends, or anonymously in a group to find someone who has previously experienced what you are experiencing and express yourself freely, and get a daily curated feed of women’s health articles and news from leading journals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Element</title>
      <link>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/project-element/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 13:41:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/project-element/</guid>
      <description>About the project In the summer of 2015, my highschool’s graduating class took up an initiative with the aim of helping students discover their passions. Working with the best of the class of 2015 in 18 different fields, they conducted a series of workshops that were attended by over 100 students along with interactive online content that benefitted over 3,000.
I was part of the design and development team that was responsible for building a framework for the interactive content for all 18 fields, the event website, and a keynote video that featured the likes of Steve Jobs and Sir Ken Robinson as narrators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Safai</title>
      <link>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/safai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 13:55:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/safai/</guid>
      <description>About the project ShriTeq 2017 was a sustainability-themed hackathon where the task to create a digital or physical solution to any existing problem in the same sector.
Being a team of 4 representing our highschool, each of us spent some time thinking up of potential problems which we could solve. After thorough discussion and debate, we decided to battle the problem of cleanliness around us.
We created Saf.ai — an app which croudsources reporting &amp;amp; cleaning of locations across the globe using our technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art4Education</title>
      <link>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/art4education/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 01:54:09 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/art4education/</guid>
      <description> About the project I worked with Art4Education during the Fall of 2016 to redesign their website and create a uniform aesthetic across their online presence.
 Art4Education is a student-driven, not for profit initiative to sponsor the education of underprivileged children by using our art and talents to raise and aggregate funds.
   The color palette    The new website     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apollo</title>
      <link>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/apollo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 13:55:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/apollo/</guid>
      <description>About the project ShriTeq 2016 was a travel-themed hackathon where we had to create a digital or physical solution to any existing problem in the same sector.
Being a team of 4 representing our highschool, each of us spent some time thinking up of potential problems which we could solve. After thorough discussion and debate, we decided to battle the problem of lengthy and monotonous travel apps.
The result was Apollo: and end-to-end travel chatbot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MINET X</title>
      <link>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/minet-x/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 23:04:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/minet-x/</guid>
      <description>About the project MINET X was my highschool’s annual technology symposium hosted by the technology club, MINET. The event brings 500+ participants together from highschools all over India to battle it out for the final trophy.
My task was to lead the design team to create everything from the event website to the branding of posters and ID cards, keeping it consistent with the ‘Make’ philosophy of the club.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Searchie</title>
      <link>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/searchie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 13:41:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/searchie/</guid>
      <description>About the project The driving force behind building Searchie was to fix the traditional recruitment process which heavily relied on a fixed group of recruiters who matched candidates according to skills, as opposed to cultural fit in an organisation, early in the recruitment process.
To clarify, recruiters and employers are not always the same.
While recruiters can be an in-house team of people who work for your company and find suitable candidates, they are often freelancers or contractors who work for multiple companies and keep nominating candidates whom they think are suitable for required roles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baymax</title>
      <link>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/baymax/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 13:42:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/baymax/</guid>
      <description>About the project The idea is pretty simple — like in the movie, we need a personal healthcare companion, someone who can help us medically when we need it to, both by providing the right information to us and helping us get in touch with the right medical professionals.
If you’ve stubbed your toe a little, Baymax will tell you how to make the swelling go away and will help you get well by providing a treatment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bharathacks</title>
      <link>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/bharathacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 13:55:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/bharathacks/</guid>
      <description>In the summer of 2017, I co-organised BharatHacks, a hackathon for solving India-specific problems. As co-organiser, I set up the website and registration apart from managing the entire venue and other logistics.
Here’s an extract from a social media post:
 This June, I’m organizing BharatHacks, a hackathon for solving India-specific problems. Programmers, designers, engineers, and entrepreneurs will come together to build products to make lives better. Organized in collaboration with Facebook Developer Circle Delhi-NCR, BharatHacks will help you take your idea forward, from hacking to raising investment and launching your product in the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://nishantgadihoke.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 11:55:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nishantgadihoke.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m Nishant Gadihoke. I’m a user experience engineer based out of Vancouver, Canada. As a UX engineer, I design meaningful products and build them using code.
With over 5 years of experience in the field while working with 10+ startups as a consultant, I have an eye for finding elegant ways to solve complex problems. Over the years, I have realised that there is no single secret recipe for building great products; instead, for me, it is a path of experimentation and leveraging my strengths to create value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://nishantgadihoke.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 11:55:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nishantgadihoke.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>You can write to me at mail@nishantgadihoke.com to which I usually respond within twenty-four hours.
Alternatively, you can add me on LinkedIn to know more about my professional career or follow me on Medium to read my thoughts. Just in the mood for a random conversation? Tweet at me or add me on Facebook.
If you’d like to discuss partnerships with Oswald Labs or need help with a product, the best way is to go to the support page on Oswald Labs’ website or write to yourfriends@oswaldlabs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>