<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Development on Nishant Gadihoke</title>
    <link>https://nishantgadihoke.com/tags/development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Development on Nishant Gadihoke</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 13:41:15 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://nishantgadihoke.com/tags/development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Oswald Labs</title>
      <link>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/oswald-labs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 13:41:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/oswald-labs/</guid>
      <description>About the project I co-founded Oswald Labs with Anand Chowdhary and Mahendra Singh Raghuwanshi in 2016 with the aim of creating technology which was accessible to everyone. Over the past few years, running this startup has taken up the majority of my time. Being a research-driven company, caring about user experience and building empathy is key to shaping our products.
While it is not possible to explain the nuances of this mega-project within the scope of this webpage, you can scroll down to read a brief description of each of the products we are currently working on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Naari</title>
      <link>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/naari/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 13:42:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/naari/</guid>
      <description>About the project Naari is the end-to-end period healthcare companion—from giving you personalized tampon recommendations using P&amp;amp;G’s survey data and HPE’s machine learning APIs, to getting those products delivered to your doorstep via Amazon.
 Great use of machine learning to drive a benefit for women.
– Erik Hasenoehrl, Research Fellow, Procter &amp;amp; Gamble
 Naari is also a social platform that lets you chat with your doctor, friends, or anonymously in a group to find someone who has previously experienced what you are experiencing and express yourself freely, and get a daily curated feed of women’s health articles and news from leading journals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Element</title>
      <link>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/project-element/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 13:41:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/project-element/</guid>
      <description>About the project In the summer of 2015, my highschool’s graduating class took up an initiative with the aim of helping students discover their passions. Working with the best of the class of 2015 in 18 different fields, they conducted a series of workshops that were attended by over 100 students along with interactive online content that benefitted over 3,000.
I was part of the design and development team that was responsible for building a framework for the interactive content for all 18 fields, the event website, and a keynote video that featured the likes of Steve Jobs and Sir Ken Robinson as narrators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Safai</title>
      <link>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/safai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 13:55:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/safai/</guid>
      <description>About the project ShriTeq 2017 was a sustainability-themed hackathon where the task to create a digital or physical solution to any existing problem in the same sector.
Being a team of 4 representing our highschool, each of us spent some time thinking up of potential problems which we could solve. After thorough discussion and debate, we decided to battle the problem of cleanliness around us.
We created Saf.ai — an app which croudsources reporting &amp;amp; cleaning of locations across the globe using our technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Searchie</title>
      <link>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/searchie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 13:41:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/searchie/</guid>
      <description>About the project The driving force behind building Searchie was to fix the traditional recruitment process which heavily relied on a fixed group of recruiters who matched candidates according to skills, as opposed to cultural fit in an organisation, early in the recruitment process.
To clarify, recruiters and employers are not always the same.
While recruiters can be an in-house team of people who work for your company and find suitable candidates, they are often freelancers or contractors who work for multiple companies and keep nominating candidates whom they think are suitable for required roles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MINET X</title>
      <link>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/minet-x/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 23:04:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nishantgadihoke.com/work/minet-x/</guid>
      <description>About the project MINET X was my highschool’s annual technology symposium hosted by the technology club, MINET. The event brings 500+ participants together from highschools all over India to battle it out for the final trophy.
My task was to lead the design team to create everything from the event website to the branding of posters and ID cards, keeping it consistent with the ‘Make’ philosophy of the club.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>