<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Branding on Nishant Gadihoke</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/branding/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Branding on Nishant Gadihoke</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 13:55:12 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/branding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Indikala</title>
      <link>http://example.org/work/indikala/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 13:55:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/work/indikala/</guid>
      <description>About the project Indikala is Asia&amp;rsquo;s premier online store for Indian handicrafts and home decor.
I led the design team to overhaul the visual identity of the store as it debuted in European and North American markets. The task was to create a unique and memorable visual identity which would resonate with existing customers and would help increase conversion rates for new ones.
The process Before rushing in to create a new brand identity, it was important to examine the previous one and observe where it worked and where it didn’t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art4Education</title>
      <link>http://example.org/work/art4education/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 01:54:09 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/work/art4education/</guid>
      <description> About the project I worked with Art4Education during the Fall of 2016 to redesign their website and create a uniform aesthetic across their online presence.
 Art4Education is a student-driven, not for profit initiative to sponsor the education of underprivileged children by using our art and talents to raise and aggregate funds.
   The color palette    The new website     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bharathacks</title>
      <link>http://example.org/work/bharathacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 13:55:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/work/bharathacks/</guid>
      <description>In the summer of 2017, I co-organised BharatHacks, a hackathon for solving India-specific problems. As co-organiser, I set up the website and registration apart from managing the entire venue and other logistics.
Here’s an extract from a social media post:
 This June, I’m organizing BharatHacks, a hackathon for solving India-specific problems. Programmers, designers, engineers, and entrepreneurs will come together to build products to make lives better. Organized in collaboration with Facebook Developer Circle Delhi-NCR, BharatHacks will help you take your idea forward, from hacking to raising investment and launching your product in the market.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>